I entirely vibe-coded this website for a project I'm working on and here's exactly how I did it.
I feel like there's a really big misconception that you can't actually make vibe-coded apps look
good or build entire applications with them and while that might have been the case a couple
months ago, the models are only going to get better and the only thing you can do is educate
yourself on how to use them. So for a little bit of context, my name is Jack, I'm 20 years old,
I currently run one of the largest vibe-coding communities in the world and I work at a startup
that does over nine million dollars a year in annual revenue. So this personal project I've
been working on essentially gives anyone the ability to create a vertical AI tool which is
an AI tool that's good at one specific thing in agent form that can do literally anything for
you. So the way that this landing page works is it's a demo where anyone can have any sort of tasks
they want to do. So maybe they want to start a cookie business or create a newsletter that sends
them the news every single morning and then it spins up a team of AI agents that are good at one
specific thing that contribute to this task. And then it uses Claude to orchestrate all these agents
that are trained on individual knowledge bases. So I'm going to show you exactly how I set this up
in my process. I made an entire video yesterday on how I set up my front end but essentially I use
Claude code inside of cursor and then I use 21stDev to get design elements that I like. So to
incorporate Claude into this project what you need is an anthropic API key. Now what I have is what
you call an AI wrapper which is just a website that is wrapped in AI. To give these agents actual skills
is I create a vector database in Pinecone for each individual agent that gives them high quality
information that isn't just data that you'd pull from the internet. And then I use Composio to give
these agents the ability to one-click integrate into pretty much any application. So it can connect to
your Gmail, your Slack, really anything you want it to. And then I use Resign to give each one of
these agents its own email address so it can email you a newsletter, email you any updates that you
want it to. Overall it's a pretty fun project to try out. Comment process and I'll send you my entire
process on how I built this as well as the link so you can try it out for yourself.